Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
[Glory]
[Episode 12]
Since you've said you want to
be my wife,
will it last for one night,
one month
or a lifetime?
Well...
You're such a strange man.
As long as we're happy together,
why do you care whether it'll
last for one night, one month
or a lifetime?
Tea seeds
will be planted in a tea plantation.
No matter how skilled I am,
I still can't guarantee
every seed can grow into a tree
for plucking leaves.
As for how long we can be married,
even if I make a promise,
it still doesn't count.
It's all up to fate.
These words don't sound like
what a good person would say.
And I definitely won't
fall into your trap.
If you don't give me a definite time,
I'm sorry but I won't follow your order.
You're in the Xinfang Pavilion now.
Mr. Yan and and Mr. Bai
live next door.
Wen is here, too.
If you still disagree
despite all my coaxing,
do I have to force you?
If this doesn't work,
I can always find someone else.
You're not allowed to go anywhere.
What? Have you changed your mind, Mr. Lu?
♪ Stars and the moon descended ♪
♪ Falling Into the mortal world
to make flowers wither and hearts break ♪
♪ How persistent ♪
♪ How can such a fleeting grace
be forgotten? ♪
♪ Beacon fires rose high ♪
♪ With one more dance,
the music is over and people are gone ♪
It's late at night.
Who else do you want to disturb?
Let's just sleep like this tonight.
Let's wait
till you give me a definite answer,
and then we can be husband and wife.
♪ We found another crescent moon ♪
I have my pride.
Please don't force me.
You're really a fool.
♪ The moon shines on the desolate hills ♪
♪ Let's lie in the sea of grass
to herd cows and sheep♪
♪ Those thoughts turned into wine,
which I drank with sorrow ♪
♪ Feeling lost, I went into my dreams
to look for the past ♪
♪ Stars and the moon descended ♪
♪ Falling Into the mortal world
to make flowers wither and hearts break ♪
♪ How persistent ♪
♪ How can such a fleeting grace
be forgotten? ♪
♪ Beacon fires rose high ♪
♪ With one more dance,
the music is over and people are gone ♪
♪ We found another crescent moon ♪
Young Master?
Murder! Murder!
The young master has been murdered!
Come quickly!
You're not in your room
early in the morning.
Mr. Bai.
Where have you been?
I woke up at midnight
and couldn't sleep due to restlessness.
I thought I'd take a walk around
and go to
that pine tree behind the courtyard
to sit for a while.
Unexpectedly...
Unexpectedly,
I fell asleep leaning against it.
I'm sorry
for being such a fool in front of you.
Mr. Bai.
Just ignore him.
He always scolds whoever he meets.
He's suspicious and full of anger.
He's just taking it out on others.
Shanbao.
That is Mr. Lu's room.
Young Master!
Yang Dingchen...
He's dead.
Grandmother selected a husband for Shanbao
out of good intentions.
Besides,
the Yang family has been on friendly terms
with our family.
Even if Shanbao had been so picky that
she didn't like him,
she still should have treated him
with courtesy
and politely seen him off
in order to save face for both families.
However, Shanbao was so arrogant and rude,
treating her suitors
as if they didn't exist,
ordering them around
and offending everyone.
She agreed to the marriage herself
but changed her mind for some reason,
leaving Mr. Yang alone
in the bridal chamber.
That's why all this trouble
has been caused.
What nonsense are you talking, Yunyin?
Yang Dingchen occupied the Qilan Garden
and set the wedding date
without permission.
Did he inform Grandmother?
And did he get permission from anyone?
He was clearly a scoundrel,
who we couldn't hit or scold.
Couldn't we at least avoid him?
Since he came to the Rong family,
he has been domineering,
arrogant and jealous.
Every young master in the Xinfang Pavilion
was once
victimized by his plots.
He made too many enemies
and got poisoned to death.
He could blame no one but himself.
But he died in the Qilan Garden after all.
I'm afraid the Yang family
won't let us off so easily.
I've warned you before.
You rejected the one who was gentle,
modest, kind and generous.
Instead, you chose him.
No wonder trouble has occurred.
Old Madam,
some men from the Yang family are here.
Grandmother, don't worry.
I will handle
my own affairs properly.
Oh, my nephew!
My dear nephew!
I'm late!
[Yang Jisheng]
-I'm late!
-Father.
My father
suddenly heard about my cousin's death.
He was overwhelmed by grief
and lost his composure.
Lady Shanbao,
please forgive him.
What? Well...
[Yang Yitang]
Well...
Everyone, don't panic.
Don't panic.
It's my fault
for not explaining this in advance.
Yitang and my late nephew
were actually twin brothers.
But when he was a kid,
he was adopted
into my branch of the family
and became my son.
The one who died
was his twin elder brother.
Everyone, don't panic.
Don't be afraid.
When Mr. Yang was a guest at our home,
he unfortunately passed away.
The Rong family
can't be absolved of the blame.
My condolences, Uncle Yang.
Let's discuss this further
inside the mansion.
Dingchen
was the most outstanding son
of our Yang family.
His death cannot remain unexplained.
Under Lord Prefect's orders,
Magistrate Lang
will personally
come to the Rong Mansion to investigate
and examine the body publicly.
Miss Rong, please allow it.
It seems to be a human footprint,
but only half of it remains.
Lady Shanbao, you're back.
I've been guarding this place with others,
and no outsiders have entered.
Open the door!
Yes!
Oh, my nephew!
-Oh, my nephew!
-Father!
Father!
-My nephew!
-Father!
My nephew!
Who was so vicious and did this?
I'm late.
Oh, my nephew!
How could the murderer be so cruel?
I will certainly
seek justice for you.
Just rest assured, my nephew.
I will definitely
seek justice for you.
How would you...
How would you expect me
to explain this to your...
After this incident,
I ordered servants to guard this place,
not allowing anyone to move the corpse,
so as to let the officials examine it.
As soon as the person I had sent
to notify the officials
just returned,
your sedan chair arrived.
My Lord, you came so quickly.
I bear a heavy responsibility
to protect the safety of the local people,
so it's my duty
to investigate the case personally.
My nephew!
Father! Father, you're an elder.
If you get so heart-broken for my cousin,
he would be unable to rest in peace.
Please take good care of yourself
so that you can take revenge
for my cousin.
He has passed away.
Master Yang, excessive grief is not good.
Now that I am here,
I will certainly try to find the culprit
and seek justice for Mr. Yang.
Start examining it!
Father.
The coroner needs to examine the body.
It's not convenient
for outsiders to stay here.
Besides, Lady Rong Shanbao is delicate
and can't see such a scene.
You'd better go out first.
I'll watch over things here.
Jie You!
Yes!
Take our guests to the main hall for tea.
-Yes.
My Lord, please.
My Lord.
No rush.
How has Old Madam Rong
been feeling lately?
Since I took office,
I've been so busy with my work
and haven't had time to pay my respects.
I feel quite ashamed.
Now that I'm in the Rong Mansion today,
I must pay her a visit.
I'll...
show you the way, My Lord.
Thank you.
As per the routines, the County Office
needs to interrogate the servants.
which might cause some inconvenience.
Please allow it, Lady Rong Shanbao.
The inspection has been finished.
My Lord.
I'd like to have a word with my brother.
Could you let me do that?
Look.
Even the Sinan jade craftsmen
couldn't
tell these two pieces of jade apart.
Back then, our mother said that
I was born only 15 minutes
later than you.
But because of these 15 minutes,
you became the official kiln porcelain
for protecting our house
while I became
the unpresentable counterfeit porcelain.
Everyone said
you were
the Yang family's most outstanding son.
However,
you're dead now.
You're dead now!
It's so good that you're dead.
Just see
how I'll use your appearance
to inherit the family property
and use my own flesh and blood
to drink the wedding wine in place of you.
I will prove to everyone in the world
that I'm actually
the most outstanding son
of the Yang family.
My dear brother.
Mr. Yang
originally lived in the Xinfang Pavilion.
I'll take you both there to have a look.
Okay. Thank you.
What a big mansion!
It's truly the style of a great family.
Even heavenly palaces
could hardly be more magnificent.
Mr. Yang was truly unfortunate.
Mr. Yan.
Officers, this way, please.
Okay.
Look over there.
What's wrong with Mr. Lu?
He's sneaking around and is so secretive.
In my opinion,
Mr. Yang
must have been killed by him.
Shut up!
If the constables hear you,
you'll be wrongly accusing
an innocent man.
That magistrate
who came to Rong Mansion today...
What?
Do you know him?
He looks quite familiar.
But I...
But I just can't remember
where I've seen him.
Lord Lang
was promoted by Prefect Xu Song
to become the Magistrate of Chunning.
He sent his calling card here
several times
but was always turned away
by the Rong family.
Today, he could finally
use the investigation as an excuse
to insist on meeting my grandmother.
In the Chongxi Hall, he fawned on us
and tried every way
to ask for money and valuables.
His behavior is truly despicable.
Just now in the room,
did you find anything?
What are you...
The bloodstain
was in an inconspicuous place.
And only half of it remained.
Outsiders could hardly identify it.
But judging from the footprint,
this person wore shoes
with pointed toecaps
as well as flat and thin soles.
There were even patterns
carved into the wooden base.
It was such an intricate design.
This must belong to a woman.
Yang Dingchen
was highly skilled in martial arts
with incredible arm strength.
What kind of woman
could sneak into the mansion and kill him?
Besides,
many people
have carved patterns on their shoe soles.
Are we supposed to catch everyone
for comparison?
But this isn't an ordinary pattern.
My Lady! Lord Lang
summoned all young ladies
and young masters to see him.
He said
he would interrogate them in court.
I'll look into it.
Grandmother gave him seven days
to investigate the case.
In the mansion, there will be constables
coming and going inevitably.
Your identity is still unclear,
and we also don't know
who your enemies are.
If you need anything,
just ask Jun Dai to do it.
Don't show yourself unnecessarily,
to avoid bringing trouble.
It's all my fault for being careless.
I didn't even notice such a small detail.
Did he really
not have that bodhi-bead bracelet on him?
Speaking of which,
this matter is so strange.
As soon as I got the message this morning,
I went there to search him.
But I truly didn't see it.
My Lady, do you think it might be...
Silence!
Yang Dingchen has done many evil things.
He deserved such an ending
due to his own deeds.
Mr. Yan, why do you have to
trouble yourself because of him?
Mr. Wen, please forgive me
for being outspoken.
People from the County Office came today.
They interrogated everyone
from the Xinfang Pavilion.
Only one person stayed in his room
without showing up.
He clearly has a guilty conscience.
In my opinion,
Mr. Yang
must have been killed by him.
If you continue to talk nonsense,
just get out of my sight,
and I won't keep you any longer.
I'm not a hereditary servant‌,
so I don't understand the etiquette
of a great family.
Young Master, you rescued me
from the pile of dead bodies.
Your kindness to me
is higher than the sky.
If Steward Lu really killed him,
he would harm you sooner or later.
How could I remain silent?
So you mean...
Lu Fusheng is the murderer?
Mr. Lu has helped you greatly
and is the loyalest and kindest person.
Don't listen to
this ignorant boy's nonsense.
He's still young and unsophisticated,
knowing nothing about importance.
Without any evidence,
we absolutely cannot
wrongly accuse an innocent person.
Mr. Wen! Mr. Wen!
Look at you. You keep talking nonsense.
You'll cause me trouble sooner or later.
One can't be kind
in a den of tigers and wolves.
Young Master,
just be careful and vigilant.
[Chongxi Hall]
One Yang died,
and another Yang has appeared.
This situation is truly frightening.
Yang Dingchen was unruly and rebellious,
like a wild beast
that had just been released from its cage
and was difficult to tame.
Though this young master looks similar,
his behavior is quite refined.
Routinely,
I need to ask you all young ladies
where you were at the time of the incident
and who can testify for you.
What a fool!
You...
Stop saying you.
You were summoned to the Rong family
to arrest the murderer.
But instead,
you mistook innocent people for suspects.
Where else could I be roaming
in the middle of the night
if I wasn't in my room?
Besides my personal maid,
where else could I find other witnesses?
Moreover,
I had no grudges against Yang Dingchen
and scarcely talked with him.
What benefit would I gain
from killing him?
Letting a foolish official like you
try the case
will only lead to wrongful convictions.
Lord Lang.
My cousin is straightforward
and outspoken.
She has offended you today.
Please forgive her
and don't mind it.
It's my fault
for trying the case improperly.
I've told you
we need to do the fortune-telling
for the wedding ceremony first
and get approval from our ancestors.
Mr. Yang
occupied our Qilan Garden
without permission.
Lady Shanbao ordered our maids
to withdraw completely.
We even gave him that courtyard.
That was already more than generous.
Even if something had gone wrong,
the Yang family's members
should be interrogated first.
They've been interrogated.
Young Master.
Lady Rong Shanbao hasn't returned yet.
Get lost!
All of you, get lost!
Last night, Yang Dingchen noticed that
Lady Rong Shanbao
still didn't return late at night.
He became furious
and drove away
all the Yang family's servants.
Lady Shanbao.
Lord Lang
isn't deliberately giving you a hard time.
Routinely,
everyone has to be interrogated.
Old Madam has agreed, too.
Since you all have a clear conscience,
What couldn't you tell others?
Xiangling.
Lord Lang hasn't interrogated you
in court.
That's already special treatment.
We'd better tell the truth
so that people won't say
we have a guilty conscience.
Lord Lang.
A few close friends of mine and I
held a tea party.
Yesterday,
it was my turn to host the party,
so I set up a tea banquet
in the Shanju Tea House.
We chatted under the moonlight,
enjoying tea and music.
We only returned at dawn.
Yunxi.
You're the owner of this tea house,
so you can say whatever you want,
can't you?
My tea house stays open all night,
specializing in
receiving aristocratic ladies‌
who enjoy night outings.
Many people in the city
can testify for me.
Yesterday, a servant from the greenhouse
suddenly came to report some good news,
saying that my rare epiphyllum
was about to bloom,
so I just invited Yunyin
to come and appreciate it.
We didn't leave until midnight.
Then we returned to our own rooms to rest.
Yunshu and I
went to the Yanyun Temple
to worship Buddha.
We listened to scriptures all day long
and closed our doors to rest early
after returning.
I suppose Yunshu did the same thing.
Alright.
Let's stop beating around the bush.
Am I the one who should be interrogated
most necessarily here?
Or it is Yunxi
or Yunshu?
All of you are trying to hide the truth
by making all kinds of excuses.
For whom are you putting on this show?
Fine.
Since none of you dare to ask,
then I'll ask.
Whose fiancé
is Yang Dingchen?
And in whose room did he die?
This is Lady Shanbao's order.
Doctor Zhao has just changed it.
Young Master!
Mr. Lu!
B-Bad news!
Over there in the hall, Lord Lang
is...is interrogating Lady Shanbao
coercively.
Your identity is still unclear,
and we also don't know
who your enemies are.
Don't show yourself unnecessarily,
to avoid bringing trouble.
Did your young master tell you
to say this?
Mr. Lu.
The Yang family won't let this go.
And the officials keep interrogating her.
How can Lady Shanbao
accept this humiliation?
You need to find a way
to help her get rid of this plight.
I got it. You may go.
I...
Enough!
The young master already said he got it.
Why are you still pestering him?
You...
-Just go now!
-You need to find a way!
-Mr. Lu!
-Hurry!
Young Master,
Lady Shanbao repeatedly told you
not to show yourself unnecessarily.
This person is trying so hard
to stir up trouble outside.
He must have ill intentions.
I know.
Lady Shanbao has her own judgment.
Young Master,
please just eat your meal and don't worry.
The food is getting cold.
Young Master, won't you have your meal?
Young Master!
Shanbao.
I have trust in your moral character.
Let me just ask you one question.
Last night
should have been your wedding night.
Why did my nephew
die alone in the bridal chamber?
And where were you?
You should give me
and the Yang family an explanation.
What wedding?
Before getting married,
the couple must enter the ancestral hall
and pay respects to the ancestors
to complete the ceremony.
Without the elders' permission
or Lady Shanbao's consent,
he forcibly occupied the house
to hold a wedding.
How was he any different from a bandit?
You only know how to make things difficult
for Lady Shanbao.
There's someone even more suspicious,
who hasn't been interrogated yet.
Mr. Bai.
At 5 AM, Mr. Yan and I
saw you returning from outside
with our own eyes.
You claimed that
you had taken a walk
outside the Xinfang Pavilion.
But I noticed
that there was mud on your boots,
and there were several peach blossoms
in your hair.
You seemed to have returned
from the garden.
Mr. Wen, so you suspect that
I killed Mr. Yang?
In the martial arts arena,
everyone saw that my strength was so weak.
I was just lucky to survive.
How could I kill him?
Moreover,
even after he died,
it wouldn't be my turn
to live in the Qilan Garden anyway.
Isn't Mr. Wen still there,
waiting for it eagerly?
Which fool would do such things
as working for someone else's benefit?
I didn't stay out all night.
Nor did I lie against my conscience.
As a scholar,
you tried to hide the truth
against your conscience like this
and said things inconsistent
with your thoughts.
Is this what the teachers have taught you?
Where on earth did you go
last night?
This is a murder case.
What can't you tell us?
Last night, he and I
were at the rockery
in the east corner of the garden,
gazing at stars and talking.
How dare you!
She admitted her own disgrace.
Yet you're still taking her side?
Yunshu, you're so pathetic.
As a daughter of the Rong family,
so what even if you had done it openly?
What kind of disgrace is this?
According to the age-old instructions
of the Rong family,
whoever dares to
hurt the Rong family's daughters
is trying to
cut off our family's bloodline.
No matter who he is,
we'll ensure
that his family property is all ruined
with no penny left.
Mr. He, you'd better think carefully.
At the tea party Yunxi hosted last night,
weren't you also a guest there, Mr. He?
Firstly,
you insulted my mother repeatedly.
And then you tried to fawn on Yunxi.
So only you're allowed to break promises,
but I can't find another better fiancé?
There's no such unfairness in the world.
Yunxi.
This is breaking a serious taboo.
Mr. He, you're so indecisive
and fickle-minded.
You've sown discord
between my two sisters
and broken the rules of the Rong family.
If Grandmother finds out about that,
the He family
definitely won't gain any benefit.
I advise you to back down
and avoid causing more trouble.
You forced me into this.
The family affairs among our sisters
can be discussed later.
Let's ask about
the important matters first.
Lady Shanbao,
we asked about your whereabouts just now,
but you were reluctant to answer.
Do you have something to hide?
I have nothing to hide.
I didn't fancy Mr. Yang,
and I was unwilling to
spend the weddning night with him,
so I simply stayed elsewhere last night.
Elsewhere?
Where exactly?
Whose place was it?
Even if I'm not asking,
they'll ask in court.
Shanbao.
If you didn't fancy Mr. Yang,
then who do you fancy?
Who did you spend the night with?
Young Master!
Young Master, you can't go!
Don't go!
You mustn't go!
You absolutely can't go!
I fell from a cliff
and was in a critical condition
while he became an official
and enjoyed success.
I can't believe
there was such a coincidence.
I'm afraid that was...
The Rong family only cares about
whether the daughters
respect their elders,
whether the sisters are united
and whether the family is prosperous.
It's up to you to choose who you love.
Unless you commit crimes
or disgrace the family's reputation,
otherwise,
the elders won't interfere.
Grandmother always commends you
for being sensible
and caring about the overall situation.
Now someone from the Yang family
has been killed.
All of us have revealed our whereabouts,
except you who keep hiding something.
Unless
your lover is a bandit or a thief,
and Mr. Yang was killed by him.
Tell us!
Don't give Lady Shanbao a hard time.
That person...
-That person is...
-Mr. Yan!
Was it you yesterday?
How dare you admit it?
I admit it.
Lady Shanbao, you and I were clearly
chatting, playing chess and painting
under the moonlight.
How come you refuse to admit it now?
What makes you think I'm unpresentable?
You...
Magistrate Lang, what?
Do you know this man?
So you're
Lady Shanbao's lover?
No wonder!
Yesterday, I accompanied Lady Shanbao
to the tea mountain.
We only came down the mountain at 5 PM.
At 7 PM, we went boating
to enjoy the scenery.
When we returned home,
we heard the night watch drum
at the city gate strike twice.
Lady Shanbao complained
that my drawing had little likeness
on the boat,
so she asked me to redraw it in my room.
By dawn,
a maid came and reported the bad news.
Only then did Lady Shanbao
leave the Xinfang Pavilion.
Actually, regarding murderous intentions,
everyone here
is a suspect.
Why do you think we're suspects?
Lady Shanbao wanted to select a husband.
Without being selected, this person
didn't blame his own incompetence.
Instead, he was only jealous of others.
By framing me after killing Mr. Yang,
he could eliminate two enemies.
Moreover, the Rong family is wealthy.
Their tea mountains and silver
are so tempting.
If Lady Shanbao is charged with murder,
the substantial family property
will be inherited by others.
Guys, don't forget that
Mr. Yang was killed at midnight
and was only discovered at dawn.
Those who had left home
could return to kill him.
Those who met with each other
could collude in their statements.
Those who testify for their whereabouts
are all servants of the Rong family.
How can their testimonies
be easily trusted?
You're accusing
all of us at a stroke.
I've never said
you're the murderer, Lady Yunxi.
Why are you so angry?
You...
What we said is all not trustworthy.
Then the murderer of this case
can never be found.
Lord Lang!
The bloody footprint in the room
has been copied.
The County Office's painter
has complemented it, too.
This shoe sole is carved
with the five-poison patterns.
The craftsmanship is exceptional.
To solve this case,
please forgive my offense for asking
which lady of the Rong family
owns this cherished item.
No wonder you've gathered us all here
with all this gossip.
So it's about this?
I don't recognize it.
Everyone is watching.
Do you expect us
to take off our shoes for inspection?
The foot is 7.1 cun long.
It's not difficult to verify it.
Measurement is conducted every year
in our mansion to make shoes.
We can check the records to find out.
Lady Shanbao.
Thanks for your help then.
Xiu Qiong.
For the sake of fairness,
Lord Lang, please
dispatch two constables to accompany us
so that we won't be suspected anymore.
Lady Yunxi's worry makes sense.
Not only the young ladies
need to be examined,
but all female servants of the Rong family
must also be examined.
Mr. Lu.
I still have a few more questions
to ask you alone.
Please.
What?
-Go!
-Let go of me!
-Cut the crap!
You knew he was avoiding the officials
and constables everywhere.
He must have his reasons.
Why did you deliberately lure him
to come here?
Mr. Yan, you're such a gentleman
and are so honest and upright.
In your mind,
there are scarcely any villains
in this world.
But this man's background is suspicious.
His intentions are dubious.
With his evasiveness,
he's surely hiding some dirty secrets.
I've done this
because I'm worried
Shanbao might be harmed by a villain.
You've done this
for your own selfish motives.
Mr. Wen.
You weren't like this before.
When...
-Since when...
-All men have jealousy.
I'm not afraid to admit it.
I'm just worried
this man has ill intentions
and will harm Shanbao.
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
You guys may leave first.
So you want to kill me?
My Lord.
I finally found you.
Don't worry.
Those who entered the mansion today
are all my trusted men.
There will be no problem.
My Lord, you used yourself as the bait.
Indeed, you made Lady Rong Shanbao
take pity on you
and rescue you.
Later, as agreed, I sent some people
to wait in that Wukui Alley for 7 days,
but there was no sign of you.
I reckoned your injuries were too severe
to recover soon,
or the Rong family
was keeping a close eye on you,
making it difficult to send messages,
so I often sent people to scout
outside the mansion.
However, every time you left the mansion,
the Rong family's members
were always by your side.
My men was afraid of alerting them
and didn't dare to approach you.
Using myself as the bait?
So you mean...
My Lord.
You took the imperial order
to investigate the murder case
of Wei Kejian
beating and killing his wife, Madam Yang.
But the Rong family is powerful,
and Lady Rong Shanbao
is quite resourceful.
Xu Song repeatedly hindered you, too.
It was very difficult to handle this case.
You said, that page boy, Qing Yun,
often eavesdropped on our conversations.
He must have ill intentions behind this.
Therefore, you took the risk yourself
by secretly infiltrating into
the Rong family.
You also told me to take the opportunity
to defect to Xu Song.
Then we could collect evidence
both openly and secretly.
Have you forgotten everything?
My Lord!
If you die,
the great credit
for solving this major case
will belong to me.
Who told you
our lord was taking risks alone?
Under His Majesty's imperial edict,
I work as the magistrate superficially,
but actually, I'm the Imperial Inspector.
I'm telling you to open the coffin
and examine the corpse.
Anyone who dares to hinder it
is defying imperial orders.
My Lord,
you're not afraid of the powerful gentry
and refuse to shield your former allies.
You always recklessly
show your ability and talent.
But you might just get killed in the end.
Let's go! Hurry!
[Making Friends through Tea
and Treating People with Courtesy]
Routinely,
I need to ask you all young ladies
where you were at the time of the incident
and who can testify for you.
What a fool!
You...
Stop saying you.
Tea table etiquette
is an essential part
of Chinese tea culture.
[Unacceptable]
It embodies the traditional spirit
of making friends through tea
and treating people with courtesy.
The spout should not point at anyone.
The teapot spout
should face a space empty of people
to avoid suggesting guests should leave.
Never flip the cup lid upside down.
Do not touch tea pets casually.
The decorations on the tea table
can only be played with
under the host's guidance.
Avoid tapping cups or scraping saucers
to express dissatisfaction.
Do not repeatedly fiddle with tea leaves.
The first serving of tea
should not be refused.
We need to repsect the tea etiquette.